<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LasgidiTour_Guide</string>
    <string name="best_hotels">Best Hotels</string>
    <string name="tourist_sites">Tourist Sites</string>
    <string name="about_lag">About Lagos</string>

    <string name="bar_title">Lasgidi Tour Guide</string>

    <string name="eko_hotel">Eko Hotel</string>
    <string name="about_eko_hotel">The Most Preferred Hotel in West Africa Eko Hotels and Suites is the most preferred hotel in West Africa,
        and it is all about the right mix! Located in the heart of Victoria Island we offer our clients a perfect blend of business and
        leisure amenities with dining and recreational options delicately infused in one amazing space. We crown all these with services that
        meet the highest international standards.
        Overlooking the new Eko Atlantic City and Atlantic Ocean, it is just a 10-minute drive to the City Centre and only 45minutes away
        from the Airport.
        Our hotels are designed for your comfort and convenience. Your security is our primary concern and you will find our customer care
        second to none.</string>


    <string name="oriental_hotel">Oriental Hotel</string>
    <string name="about_oriental_hotel">Lagos Oriental Hotel is a 5-Star luxury hotel situated in-between the Lekki and Victoria Island areas of Lagos.
        Located at 3, Lekki Road, Victoria Island, the Lagos Oriental Hotel is within proximity of numerous business and tourist attractions.
        The Nike Art Gallery is 10 minutes away; it’s an excellent spot for international guests. When entering the Lagos Oriental Hotel, you feel
        an atmosphere inspired by a dynamic modernity. All facilities, from the Chinese Restaurant, the Japanese Gourmet Restaurant, the Lobby
        Lounge and Bar’s and the Grand Ballroom to the guest rooms and suites, meet the most exacting demands for comfort and service. Hospitality
        in the best Lagos Oriental Hotel tradition has been reborn.</string>

    <string name="de_rembrandt_hotel">De Rembrandt Hotel</string>
    <string name="about_de_rembrandt_hotel">De Rembrandt Hotel and Suites is a 4 star luxury hotel located in the heart of Ikeja, Lagos.
        The hotel is two blocks from the Ikeja City Mall, Shoprite,the governor’s office and a lot of other prominent attractions.
        The fifty rooms, six floors hotel is a magnificent edifice just on the busy Awolowo road. The property is twenty minutes away from the
        popular Computer Village market, thirty minutes away from the the local airport, and 35 minutes away from the international airport.
        The strategic location of our hotel gives you easy access to many companies in Ikeja.</string>

    <string name="ibis_hotel">Ibis Hotel</string>
    <string name="about_ibis_hotel">Hotel Ibis is a luxury hotel located at 23 Toyin Street, Ikeja, Lagos, Nigeria. Hotel Ibis is 8.40 km,
        approximately 10 minutes, from the Murtala Mohammed Airport (MMA). Hotel Ibis has 165 well-furnished and air-conditioned Standard rooms;
        free Wi-Fi available in each. The rooms have sweet Ibis bedding, a coffee machine, an LCD screen TV, en-suite bathrooms and full-length
        windows. Each bathroom has a shower and a hair dryer. The exquisite parquet flooring definitely assures you of sweet steps of comfort,
        making you as relaxed as possible.</string>

    <string name="rollace_hotel">Rollace Hotel</string>
    <string name="about_rollace_hotel">Stay at one of Lagos’ most beautiful hotels: Rollace Hotel Ajao Estate. You will undoubtedly love the
        well-preserved, original charm of our hotel. Your stay at Rollace Hotel with our personal, welcoming service, modern hotel facilities
        and family-friendly hotel will be an unforgettable experience. A delicious breakfast, friendly front desk assistance and a great night’s
        rest in an impeccably clean room: At Rollace Hotel Lagos, our staffs are always on hand to help with a smile to make your stay perfect down
        to the last detail. We welcome you to stay at Rollace Hotel Lagos and experience our unsurpassed service and warm, homely atmosphere for yourself. </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>